Morning's here
아침이 찾아왔네
The morning's here
Sunshine is here
해님은 방긋, 하늘은 활짝
아침이 찾아왔네
The sky is clear
The morning's here
- 아침이 찾아왔네
- 아저씨!
Hey!
Do you have to do that?
It's Saturday!
꼭 이 래 야 돼 요?
토요일이 라구요
Oh, come on!
왜 이 래요
아침이 찾아왔어요
Morning's here!
아침이 찾아왔네
해님은 방긋
나나나나나...
I hate this apartment!
난 이 아파트 싫어
I hate this wall color!
I hate that it still smells like bird!
이 벽 색깔도 싫어
날개 달린 짐승 냄새도 싫어
I hate that singing guy!
저 딴따라도 싫고
Are you kidding? I love that guy!
무슨 소리야
난 그 아저씨 좋던데
Morning's here
아침이 찾아왔네
아침이 찾아...
Stop it!
시끄럿!
I will kill you.
죽는 수가 있다!
I hate that my room is so small.
내 방도 너무 작아
I have all the space I need.
Do what I did.
난 충분하던데
나처럼 해봐
You don't even have a bed.
You sleep in a ball on the floor!
넌 침대도 없이
바닥에 구겨져서 자잖아
I am tired of your bellyaching.
네 불평에는 이제 질렸다
내가 얼마나 힘들게 꾸몄는데
I've worked hard to make this
a nice place for us.
I know.
I'm so sorry.
- 알아, 정말 미안하다
- 괜찮아
I'm sorry, okay?
- 거봐, 훌륭한 아파트잖아
- 시끄러, 이건 개집이야
It's a great apartment!
Shut up!
This place is a hole!
The One with All the Haste
I still can't believe
you've got an earring!
자기가 귀를 뚫었다니
아직도 믿어지지 않아
I know, I know.
Who am l? David Bowie?
그래, 내가 누구지?
데이빗 보위?
He does that?
- 그 사람이 그래?
- 내가 알 게 뭐야
I don't know. Whatever.
I think it makes you look
really dangerous.
- 아주 위험한 사람처럼 보여
- 나도 알아
Oh, I know.
You know what?
아는지 모르지만
I never would've gotten this
if it weren't for you.
자기가 아니었으면
이런 거 절대 안 했어
진심이야
자기랑 있으면 난...
When I'm with you, I'm like...
...this whole other guy.
I love that guy!
전혀 다른 사람이 돼
너무나 사랑스럽지
I mean, I love you too.
A lot.
물론 자기도 사랑하지만
But that guy!
또 다른 내 모습도
마음에 쏙 들어
I love that guy!
I love both of you.
난 둘 다 좋아
I wish I didn't have to go.
안 갔으면 좋겠다
Then don't.
그럼 가지 마
Stay here.
Don't go so soon to London.
여기 그냥 있어
더도 말고 딱 하루만
Just one more day.
- 로스, 이럼 또 힘들어지잖아
- 하루만, 정말이야
Please don't do this to me again.
I'd stay, but I've already missed
so much work. They'll fire me.
나도 있고는 싶지만
이렇게 놀다간 해고당할 거야
So? Then you could stay
as long as you want.
그럼 눌러앉을 수 있겠네
I wish I could.
나도 그러고 싶어
Oh, no. Don't start packing.
안돼, 제발 짐 싸지 마
부탁이야, 확 그냥!
Come on!
I don't think you understand packing.
그건 짐을 푸는 거야
막판에 허둥대긴 싫어
I don't want to leave it till last.
Last time, I left my knickers here.
지난번엔 속옷까지
놓고 갔다니까
Yeah, I know.
I tried them on.
알아, 내가 입어봤어
You didn't!
농담이겠지
No, I didn't.
I didn't want to be "that guy."
맞아, '저런 녀석'이
될 순 없지
얘들아
호! 호! 호!
Excuse me?
- 뭐라고?
- 그 바지
Your pants.
Oh yeah! You like them?
그래, 맘에 들어?
I went to a used-clothes store
and got maternity stuff.
중고매장에서 임신복 몇 벌
골라왔어, 이거 진짜 편하다
These are so comfortable.
Pheebs, those are Santa pants.
피비, 그건 산타 바지야
- 뭐?
- 산타 바지라고
Santa pants.
Santa Claus' pants.
산타클로스 바지
No. They're maternity pants.
아냐, 임산부 바지야
봐, 아기 이름 명단도 줬어
They even came with
a list of baby names. See?
어때
These names are good,
and these are bad.
이쪽은 좋은 이름
이쪽은 나쁜 이름
- 안녕
- 우리 왔어
Hey, Phoebes.
안녕, 피비
So, how are the elves?
꼬마요정들은 잘 있니?
I don't know.
How are the...you know?
잘 모르겠네요
그러는 댁은...
Your clothes aren't funny.
네 옷은 재미없다
What should I wear to a Knicks game?
나 닉스 게임에
뭐 입고 가지?
A T-shirt that says,
"l Don't Belong Here"?
'괜히 왔네'가 박힌 티셔츠?
You have tickets?
닉스 티켓이 있어?
Mom got Dad's season tickets in
the divorce, so she gave them to me.
이혼하실 때 엄마가
아빠한테서 뺏은 시즌티켓이야
Apparently, they're good seats.
자리도 아주 좋아
Oh, my God!
Those are almost on the floor!
이런, 코트 바로 옆이잖아
우디 앨런 만나서 이력서 줄래
I could slip Woody Allen my resume.
Do you guys want these?
이거 갖고 싶어?
Yeah, we do!
- 당연하지
- 물론
그럼 가져
Well, you got them!
- 고맙다
- 대신 우리 집 돌려줘
Just give us our apartment back.
Oh, I didn't see that coming.
그런 심오한 뜻이...
Are you serious?
진심이야?
Come on.
We know what these are worth.
이거 왜 이래, 우리도
이 티켓의 가치는 알아
Do you think we're stupid?
우리가 무슨 바보니?
Not stupid.
You're meaner than I thought.
바보는 아닌데
생각보다 치사하다
What do you say?
어떡할래?
Forget it. I'm not giving up my
bachelor pad for basketball seats.
됐네요, 내 독신생활의 터전을
그깟 농구 티켓과 맞바꾸다니
Your "bachelor pad"?
독신생활의 터전?
Have you even had a girl here?
여자나 데려와 봤어?
No.
아니
But Joey has, and I usually
talk to them in the morning.
이 몸은 보통 조이가 끌어들인
여자들과 아침에 대화를 나누지
Yeah, you do!
당당하게 살아라
Come on!
이러지 마
Gunther, can I get
two cups of chino, please?
건터, 카푸치노
두 잔 부탁해요
Good one.
재미있네
Come on.
Season tickets!
야, 시즌티켓이라고
시즌티켓이 뭔지 알아?
Season tickets!
You know what that means?
I'm not giving up the apartment.
잊어버려
아파트는 포기 못해
들어봐, 내가 어렸을 때
When I was a kid, my dad's company
gave season tickets...
아버지 회사에서 매년 최고실적
영업사원한테 그 티켓을 줬는데
...to the No. 1 salesman
every year. My dad never won.
아버지는 한 번도 못 탔어
Of course, he wasn't in sales.
But still, I never forgot that!
물론 영업부 소속은 아니셨지만
난 그걸 결코 잊을 수가 없어
Hey guys!
- 얘들아
- 그래
Oh, my God!
얼라려?
We don't make enough
fun of you already?
아예 무덤을 파지 그러냐
Oh, yeah.
Emily convinced me to do it.
이거? 에밀리가 하랬어
You do know that Wham broke up?
그룹 웸 해체된 건 알고 있냐?
I like it. Emily likes it.
That's what counts.
난 좋아, 에밀리도 좋아하고
그럼 됐잖아
So, how are you guys doing?
너희들은 별일 없니?
Don't try and talk all normal
with that thing in your ear.
귀에 그딴 걸 달고 감히
평범한 대화를 하시겠다?
Where's Emily?
에밀리는 어디 있어?
She's saying goodbye
to her uncle.
삼촌한테 작별 인사하러 갔어
Didn't she, like, just get here?
- 온 지 얼마 안됐잖아
- 누가 아니래!
Easy, tiger.
뚜껑 열릴라
I just hate this so much.
속상해 죽겠다
Every time I go pick her up at
the airport, it's so great.
공항에 마중 나갈 때면
가슴이 설레지만
But I'm thinking, "I'll be right back
in a couple of days, dropping her off."
며칠 후에 다시 그 자리에
배웅하러 나와야 하거든
-So what'll you do?
-There's nothing to do.
그래서 어떡할 거야
뭘 어떡해, 난 여기 살고
에밀리는 런던에 사는데
She lives there.
I live here.
거처를 옮기면 모르지만
오라고 하면 어떨까
She'd have to move here.
She should move here.
What?
뭐?
-I can ask her to live with me.
-Are you serious?
같이 살자고 해야겠어
- 제정신이야?
- 안 될 거 있나?
-I mean, why not?
-You've only known her six weeks!
만난 지 6주밖에 안됐잖아
I've got a carton of milk in my fridge
I've had a longer relationship with.
우리 냉장고의 우유도
그보다는 오래됐겠다
Look, guys, when I'm with her,
it's like....
에밀리와 함께 있으면...
난 훨씬 멋진 남자로 변해
She brings out this great side of me.
I mean, I love her, you know?
에밀리를 사랑해, 알아?
And I love the milk!
나도 우유 사랑해
But I won't ask some British girl
to move in with me.
그렇다고 영국 여자랑
살려고 하진 않아
Joey, you say things now.
이쯤해서 네가 수습해라
Look, Ross. He's right.
Emily's great.
로스, 얘 말이 맞아
물론 에밀리는 멋진 여자야
She's great!
But this is too soon.
You'll only scare her.
하지만 너무 빨라
괜히 부담만 주게 돼
I don't want to do that.
- 나도 그건 싫어
- 그럼
You don't want to wreck it.
Don't go too fast.
너무 서두르면 다 틀어져
No. You're right.
I know, you're right.
그래, 너희들 말이 옳다
아무 말 안 할래
I'm not going to do it.
-Thanks guys.
-No problem.
- 그래, 고맙다
- 별말을 다 하네
Just remember to wake us up
before you go-go.
'그대 떠나기 전 우릴 깨워 주'
It's too hard. Too hard!
속 뒤집혀서 못해먹겠다
All right.
Last chance for the tickets.
좋아, 얘들아
마지막 기회야
Otherwise, I give them to my
new boyfriend, Joshua.
까딱하면 내 남자친구
조슈아한테 넘어간다
No, thank you.
사양하렵니다
Wait, wait. Come on, come on!
Let's trade.
잠깐 대기
그냥 바꾸자
The timing's perfect!
I just clogged the toilet!
타이밍도 그만이야
방금 변기 막혔거든
I want those seats. But we can't live
in the small apartment...
나도 너만큼 갖고 싶지만
다시 좁은 데로는 못 들어가
...after living here!
Ever read Flowers for Algernon?
'알제논의 꽃다발'도
안 읽어봤냐?
읽었네요, 그러는 넌 '스포츠
일러스트레이티드' 읽어봤어?
Ever read Sports Illustrated?
No, I didn't read yours!
안 읽었다, 어쩔래
We can go to the game tonight!
오늘 게임도 볼 수 있어
The only way I'll consider this is...
시즌티켓 정도로는 절대
내 마음을 바꿀 수 없어
...if they offer more
than just season seats.
-It's the Knicks!
-Screw the Knicks!
- 닉스 경기잖아
- 얼어죽을 닉스!
I didn't mean that.
I just meant that...
그런 뜻이 아니고
아파트가 훨씬
가치 있단 얘기지
...the apartment is worth
so much more.
And the Knicks rule.
- 닉스가 대빵이야
- 고럼! 대빵이지
Yeah, the Knicks rule!
So? Are you going to do it?
그래서 바꿀 거야?
No, we're not going to
because it's not an even trade.
아니, 그럴 순 없어
이건 거래가 안 되니까
그럼 이건 어때
All right, look.
What if you could keep the apartment
and the tickets?
너희가 아파트도 갖고
표도 가질 수 있다면?
Done!
좋시다!
Let me finish. I'm talking about a bet.
Winner takes all.
끝까지 들어, 내기야
이기는 쪽이 다 갖기
We could get nothing.
- 개털 될 수도 있겠네?
- 다 가질 수도 있지
Or everything.
I like that.
그게 훨 좋다
What do you say?
- 어떡할래?
- 싫어요
Just do it!
- 까불지 말고!
- 어라? 협박까지?
Oh! I'm convinced!
Come on, man!
You know I'd do it for you.
나라면 널 위해
기꺼이 했어
Because you're my best friend.
넌 둘도 없는 친구니까
All right. But you can't
use that again for a whole year.
좋아, 대신 너 앞으로
1년 간 그거 써먹지 마
I'm in.
- 해보자
- 좋았어!
This is so exciting!
What are you going to bet?
진짜 재미있겠다
뭘로 내기할 거야?
We should let Phoebe decide...
피비한테 맡기자, 객관적인
입장이면서도 너무 예쁘니까
...because she's the only one
who's impartial, and she's so pretty.
좋아
I have a game!
오, 있다!
- 그래, 좋았어
- 제대로 찾았다
-This is great!
-What's the game?
무슨 게임인데
딱히 제목은 없어
아니다, '피비 볼'
It doesn't have a name.
No, okay. Phoebe Ball!
No, it doesn't have a name.
아냐, 제목 없어
좋아, 모니카
나무의 어떤 점이 좋죠?
What is your favorite thing
about trees?
-They're green?
-Good! Five points!
- 푸르다?
- 좋았어, 5점!
잘했어요
그럼 조이...
동일한 질문
Same question.
-They're tall.
-Three points!
- 키가 크다
- 오, 3점
둘 다 훌륭한 답이지만
난 '잎이 무성하다'를 원했어
Both fine answers, but we were
looking for leafy. Leafy.
That's not even a game.
이건 게임도 아냐
시끄러, 이기고 있잖아
Shut up. We're winning!
You want to finish this?
We get a deck of cards.
단판승부로 끝낼까?
높은 카드를 집는 쪽이
이기는 거야, 어때
High card wins.
What do you say?
-Let's do it!
-Oh, I have cards!
좋아, 하자
- 나한테 카드 있어
- 잘됐네
Yeah. Here.
자, 여기...
얘는 마술용이고, 그렇지
No, these are the trick deck.
Here, yes.
맞아, 이거다
- 여기
- 너희가 먼저 집어
Okay, you guys pick first.
- 좋아
- 그래
-Four.
-That's a low one!
- 4...
- 바닥 쳤음다!
You look.
I can't do it.
- 피비? 난 차마 못 보겠다
- 누군 강심장이니?
What makes you think I can?
알았어
Ace!
에이스!
Why are you hugging?
- 너흰 왜 껴안고 난린데
- 우리 집을 되찾게 됐잖아
We won our apartment back!
What? Ace is high!
Jack, queen, king, ace!
뭐? 에이스가 높지
잭, 퀸, 킹, 에이스
No! Ace is low!
Ace, two, three, four!
에이스가 왜 높아
에이스, 2, 3, 4
I don't know.
난 몰라
Look it!
보시라, 아하...
Come on, pick again!
- 그럼 다시 하자
- 자, 이리 줘
좋아
간다
Come on, apartment!
오너라, 아파트!
I know queen is high!
퀸이 좀 높지롱!
김칫국부터 드시나...
Not as high as....
It worked! King!
됐다, 킹!
We pick again!
- 안돼, 다시 해
- 왜?
-Why?
-I don't know.
몰라
Tickets, please.
표 주실까요?
Courtside, baby!
코트 옆이거덩!
Seriously, good game, though.
Good game.
멋진 한 판이었어요
What are they so mad about?
They got the apartment back.
왜 화를 내지?
집 찾아갔잖아
No, they didn't.
전혀 아니올시다
나야
Packed while you were gone.
없는 동안 짐 좀 쌌어
I left knickers under your pillow.
베개 밑에 속옷 몇 장 뒀어
Move in with me?
나랑 같이 살자
What?
뭐?
Don't be scared. It sounds crazy,
and people will say it's too soon...
겁먹지 마
너무 서두른다고 주위에선
정신 나갔다고들 하겠지만
...but just think.
Think how great it would be.
얼마나 좋을지 생각해봐
난 모르겠어
I don't know.
런던을 떠나다니...
Leaving London....
My whole family lives there....
- 가족들도 다 거기 있는데
- 알아
-My job.
-You'll get a job here.
- 직장문제에다...
- 여기서도 일할 수 있어
I always hear about them foreigners
stealing American jobs.
그런 얘기 많잖아
외국인들이 미국인의 일자리를
뺏는다고, 자기도 할 수 있어
That could be you.
Yeah, but it's my whole life.
하지만 내 모든 게 거기 있어
You come to England.
자기가 영국으로 와
I would. I really would.
But my son is here.
안돼, 나도 가고는 싶지만
아들을 두고 떠날 순 없어
I can't leave him.
You don't think there's any way?
달리 방법이 없을까?
별로 없을 거야
I don't think so.
It would be different if it was
way into the future...
장래를 약속한다면 또 모르지
예를 들어 결혼을 한다거나
...and we were getting married.
What?
뭐?
Right. I shouldn't have said "married."
Please don't go freaky on me.
아냐, 결혼이란 말을
꺼내는 게 아닌데
제발 겁내지 마
I didn't mean it.
I take it back.
그런 뜻이 아니었어
못 들은 걸로 해
No. Don't.
아냐, 됐어
Why don't we?
하면 되지
Why don't we what?
하다니, 뭘?
Get married.
결혼 말이야
You are mad!
- 미쳤구나
- 아니, 진심이야
No, I'm not! It's perfect.
It's better than you moving here.
동거하는 것보다 백 번 나아
난 영원히 함께 있고 싶으니까
It's us together forever,
and that's what I want.
-We've known each other six weeks!
-I know.
우린 만난 지 6주밖에 안됐어
그게 대체 무슨 상관이야
안 된다는 법이라도 있나?
So what? Who's to say?
Does that mean we can't do it?
Look. I was with Carol for
four years before we got married...
난 캐롤하고 4년이나
사귀다 결혼했지만
...and I wound up divorced
from a pregnant lesbian.
결국 레즈비언
임산부한테 이혼 당했어
I mean, this....
이건 우리니까
가능한 얘기야
This makes sense for us.
Our first date, we ended up
spending the whole weekend in Vermont.
우리 처음 만난 날 버몬트로
날아가 주말을 함께 보냈고
I mean, last night I got my ear pierced.
Me!
어제 난 귀도 뚫었어, 내가!
This feels right.
잘못된 건 없어
안 그래?
Doesn't it?
My parents will be really mad.
엄마아빠가 펄쩍 뛰시겠네
Are you saying, "Yes"?
Is that "Yes"?
그 말은 허락한다는 뜻이야?
Yes.
그래
- 정말? 우리 결혼하는 거야?
- 오, 세상에
-We're getting married!
-Oh, my God!
We're getting married!
우리가 결혼하다니
Come here, come here.
이리 와봐
Emily, will you marry me?
나와 결혼해주겠어?
그래
좀 작다
It's a bit small.
Damn! I thought that'd be
romantic as hell.
젠장, 이럼 무진장
로맨틱할 줄 알았는데
It was.
감동적이야
Those were, like,
the best seats ever!
- 좌석 진짜 환상이더라
- 그러게
Should we give these to the girls?
Like a peace offering?
야, 화해의 뜻으로
이건 여자애들 줄까?
That's very nice.
Plus, they were free and too small.
그거 좋은 생각이다
공짜에다 사이즈도 작잖아
Oh, God!
어럽쇼?
Hey, you want a beer?
맥주 마실래?
- 으악!
- 나도 알아!
I know!
Open up! Open up! Open up!
문 열어! 문 열어! 문 열어!
We'll discuss it in the morning.
날 밝으면 얘기합시다
What the hell is going on?
이런 경우가 어디 있나
We took our apartment back!
우리 집을 되찾은 것 뿐이야
I had nothing to do with it.
난 아무 관계없다!
Okay, it was my idea.
But I don't feel good about it.
내 생각이었지만
기분은 찜찜해
We are switching back right now.
원위치로 돌려놔, 당장
No, we're not.
We're not leaving!
싫어, 그렇게는 못해
You'll have to.
You both have jobs.
너희 둘 다 직장에 다니니까
집 비우는 즉시 원상복귀야
As soon as you do, we'll switch back!
You can't stop us.
우릴 막을 순 없어
맞지, 조이?
-Right, Joe?
-I don't know.
글쎄다...
What?
뭐?
I don't want to move again, with....
이 짐을 또 옮기자면... 에이
This is our apartment
and they stole
상관없어, 여긴 우리 집이야
쟤들이 훔쳤어, 날강도들아!
You stole!
Our apartment!
We won it fair and square. Twice!
정당한 방법으로 따낸 집이야
두 번이나, 꼭 되찾고 말겠어
And I am getting it back right now!
I'm getting it back right now!
당장 내놔!
All right.
좋아
We figured you might respond
this way, so we have a backup offer.
이렇게 나올 줄 알았어
제안 하나만 할게
No more offers.
You can't offer anything to us!
싫어, 너희는 이제
내놓을 게 없어
-Let us keep the apartment and
-As a thank you...
이 아파트를 돌려주면...
감사의 뜻으로...
...Rachel and I will kiss
for one minute.
우리가 1분 동안 키스해줄게
-Totally worth it!
-That was one good minute!
제값 받았다
환상의 1분이었어
Good night.
- 잘 자라
- 쉬어
-Men are such idiots.
-I know.
남자들은 다 바보라니까
누가 아니래, 고작 그 정도로
아파트를 선뜻 토해 내다니
Can you believe something that stupid
actually got us our apartment back?
If you had just done that
after the last contest...
그러게 진작 그걸 해줬으면
왔다 갔다 할 필요 없었잖아
...no one would have
had to move at all.
Let's pretend that's not true.
- 못 들은 걸로 하자
- 그래
됐다, 스카프 완성
Scarf's done.
Come on, come on!
- 어서 들어와
- 알았어
- 왔니?
- 안녕
What's going on?
- 무슨 일이야?
- 중대발표가 있대
Ross has some big thing
to tell everyone.
좋아, 그러니까...
Emily and l, we decided...
에밀리하고 나
결혼하기로 했어
...to get married.
What?
뭐?
Oh, are you pregnant too?
거기도 임신했어요?
아뇨
No.
When did
How did you
언제... 어쩌다...
We just decided to go for it.
그냥 결정을 내렸어
We know it's a bit hasty...
좀 이른 감이 있지만
그게 옳은 것 같아서
...but it just feels so right.
I was just telling the guys
- 방금 애들한테...
- 그래, 나도 들었어
Yeah, I heard.
I think it's great!
멋지다
정말 잘됐다
I'm so happy for you!
Well, yeah!
Congratulations!
- 우리도 축하해
- 그럼
I can't believe
you're getting married!
- 정말 결혼하는 거야?
- 그래
Monica and Rachel made out.
모니카랑 레이첼이랑 했다
Morning's here
아침이 찾아왔네
The morning's here
Sunshine is here
해님은 방긋, 하늘은 활짝
아침이 찾아왔네
The sky is clear
The morning's here
-Hey, you're back!
-Hey, get into gear
- 자네 돌아왔구먼
- 하루를 준비하세
Breakfast is near
식탁을 차려보세
The dark of night has disappeared
어두운 밤 저 멀리 사라졌네
I'll see you tomorrow morning!
- 내일 아침에 보세
- 그러죠